始而复终
Begin where it ends
终而复始
End to begin
去敲那扇门
Knock on that door
你才能进去
So you can get in
别在意时间
And don't mind the time
忘记过去
Forget all that's been
在公园中迷路
Get lost in the park
找到那棵活着的树
Find a tree that will last
找到那条密道
Find a secret path
导向她家的密道
That leads to her house
用楼梯爬到楼顶
Climb the stairs to the roof
平平地躺下
Lay flat on your back
没必要伤心
No use feelin down
没必要皱眉
Get rid of that frown
晒着太阳
Take a walk
走走吧
On the sunnyside
晒着太阳走走吧
Take a walk on the sunnyside of
在小溪里洗一下手
Wash up in a stream
让水带走你
Let it take you away
穿越山川
Through forests and seas
不管到哪儿
Wherever it may
让空气中充满着你自身的韵律
Fill up the space with your own melodies
每次
And every once in a while
你不高兴的时候
When you miss the breeze
看看你膝盖的伤口
Just look at the scars marking your knees
再次明白你的悲伤早已飘散
And know that again now it's where it's at
没必要伤心
No use feelin down
没必要皱眉
Get rid of that frown
晒着太阳
Take a walk
走走吧
On the sunnyside
晒着太阳在城镇上走走吧
Take a walk on the sunnyside of town
但是当乌云
But when the clouds
密布的时候
Come closing in
你察觉到雨滴击打在你的皮肤上
You feel the raindrops on your skin
让它下吧
Let it pour
别介意这些
Let it be okay
直到你
Until you know
遇到下一个晴天
Another sunnyday
没必要伤心
No use feelin down
没必要皱眉
Get rid of that frown
晒着太阳
Take a walk
走走吧
On the sunnyside
晒着太阳在城镇上走走吧
Take a walk on the sunnyside of town